Finding aid for the Jerry Lewis papers LSC.2124
UCLA Library Special Collections
Jerry Lewis papers
1956-2012
UCLA Library Special Collections
Lewis, Jerry
LSC.2124
73.4 Linear Feet (6 record carton boxes, 27 document boxes, 3 flat boxes)
Charles Jeremy Lewis was an American politician who served in the California State Assembly from 1969 to 1979 and then the US House of Representatives from 1979 to 2013. This collection contains papers, photographs, and videotapes which were formerly held by Lewis's congressional office and transferred to UCLA upon his retirement in 2013. The materials document the work done by Lewis over his half century of involvement in local, state, and federal politics, containing everything from election records to legislative background material to personal correspondence.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Donated by Jerry Lewis, 2012.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9974252173606533
Biography/History
Charles Jeremy Lewis was born in Seattle, Washington, on October 21, 1934. He grew up primarily in California, however, graduating from San Bernardino High School in 1952 and UCLA in 1956. After receiving his BA, Lewis returned to the Inland Empire and worked for many years as a successful insurance broker. In 1964, he decided to run for a position on the San Bernardino City Unified School District board, which he won and held until 1968. His appetite for politics whetted, in 1966 he worked on the staff of Jerry Pettis, who was elected to Congress to represent California's 33rd district. In 1968, Lewis made a run of his own to represent California's 73rd district, encompassing eastern San Bernardino, in the California State Assembly.
Lewis served in the Assembly for ten years, authoring a number of pieces of legislation which would prove to have significant statewide and national impact. In 1972, he authored the Child Development Act, which consolidated all child care and preschool programs into one overarching program managed by the Department of Education. In 1976, he wrote legislation that created the South Coast Air Quality Management District, which has been one of the main drivers of air quality improvement in Southern California. Lewis made an unsuccessful bid for California State Senate in 1974, but four years later pulled off a successful run to represent California's 37th Congressional district in the 96th United States Congress.
Over the next thirty four years, Jerry Lewis was reelected by the people of the Inland Empire sixteen times, never with lower than 61% of the vote. In his second term, he was appointed to the US House of Representatives Committee on Appropriations, where he would remain until his retirement in 2012. His position on this committee—including a stint as chairman from 1999 to 2005—gave him the power he needed to pursue an extensive legislative agenda. Nationally, Lewis worked to uncover fraud and expand oversight of federal agencies. But his most lasting achievements were his work on land, water, and energy issues facing the state of California. The construction of the Seven Oaks Dam, designed to prevent the disastrous flooding which was once common in the area, as well as numerous efforts to reduce fire risk in the San Bernardino Mountains, can all be credited to Lewis's dedicated committee work.
Organization and Arrangement
This collection has been arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Public Relations, 1956–2012
Subseries 1.1: Press Clippings, 1969–2012
Subseries 1.2: Press Releases, 1979–2005
Subseries 1.3: District Mailers, 1971–2007
Subseries 1.4: Correspondence, 1969–2012
Subseries 1.5: Travel, Events, and Speeches, 1956–2012
Series 2: Election Campaigns, 1968–2010
Subseries 2.1: California State Assembly, 1968–1978
Subseries 2.2: California State Senate, 1973–1976
Subseries 2.3: United States Congress, 1970–2010
Subseries 2.4: Other Campaigns and Appointments, 1968–1993
Series 3: Legislative Files, 1969–2013
Subseries 3.1: California State Assembly, 1969–1978
Subseries 3.2: US Congress, California Subject Files, 1979–2013
Subseries 3.3: US Congress, National Subject Files, 1979–2013
Series 4: Media, 1961–2012
Series 5: Electronic calendar print outs, budget requests, and CDs, 1996-2009
Scope and Content
Jerry Lewis's political career spanned almost a half century, from his election to the San Bernardino City Unified School District board in 1964 until his retirement as representative of California's 41st district in 2013. In that time, his offices collected a remarkable amount of material relating to his career as a legislator. The collection contains internal memoranda, external correspondence, photographs, maps, posters, legislative information, artifacts, memorabilia, and most of all background documentation on the many local, state, and national issues that Lewis was most concerned with.
The most unique material in this collection is contained in Series 1 (Public Relations), Series 2 (Election Campaigns), and Series 4 (Media). The first series contains documentation relating to the daily operation of Lewis's offices: press clippings on Lewis and his legislative activities, copies of press releases and office mailings, correspondence with constituents and fellow politicians, and travel and event documentation. The second series consists of documentation relating to every election that Lewis ran in from his first campaign for California State Assembly in 1968 to his second to last campaign for Congress in 2008. Finally, the fourth series contains all of the video tapes, photographs, and books maintained by his office, including video tape masters of commercials from Lewis's first campaign for Congress in 1978 and hundreds of photographs of Lewis with everyone from constituents visiting DC to Ronald Reagan to the comedian Jerry Lewis. Since the majority of the material in these three series does not exist elsewhere, researchers interested in understanding the internal workings of Jerry Lewis's congressional office will find these sections to be invaluable.
The remaining material, contained in Series 3 (Legislative Records), covers the many local, state, and national subjects that Lewis was concerned with during his time in both the California State Assembly and the US House of Representatives. There are also reams of documentation produced by Lewis and other office members indicating their opinions on issues and strategies they planned to take in passing legislation. This material may be of great benefit to a researcher concerned with minute details of particular issues or the internal workings of the House Appropriations committee.
Lewis, Jerry
- Series 1: Public Relations, 1956-2012
  Scope and Content
  Jerry Lewis's offices maintained records of all newspaper coverage generated on the congressman, as well as all official statements issued to his constituents and to the press during his nine years in the California State Assembly and thirty four years in the U.S. House of Representatives. This series consists of newspaper press clippings, which include articles written by Jerry Lewis and all mentions of Jerry Lewis by the press; press releases his office circulated to the news media; and district mailers sent to his constituency. Some of the records were only kept intermittently, but overall the series spans from 1969 to 2012, covering almost his full political career in the Assembly and Congress. The district mailers and press releases discuss issues most important to Lewis, such as congressional spending and the California Desert Protection Act. The press clippings include mentions of Lewis in relation to everything from major national issues, such as the Iran-Contra Affair, to local town hall meetings. Researchers may be interested in the drafts, revisions, and notes included in some of these files, mostly in the press releases, which give insight into the crafting of Lewis's public messages.
  - Subseries 1.1: Press Clippings, 1969-2012
    This subseries, which is one of the largest in the collection, consists primarily of newspaper clippings that mention or feature Jerry Lewis and spans almost his entire career, from his tenure as a California State Assemblyman starting in 1969 to his retirement from the United States Congress in 2012. Lewis's office obtained the clippings almost exclusively from Allen's Press Clipping Bureau and they include both articles from local newspapers, such as the San Bernardino County Sun, and nationally syndicated papers, such as the Los Angeles Times. The clippings cover a wide variety of national and local topics, including California elections, Lewis's positions on the Gulf War and the Iraq War, the AIDS crisis in the 1980s, the debate over the inclusion of the Mojave National Preserve in the California Desert Protection Act in the 1990s, Lewis's response to the September 11, 2001 attacks, his trip to Baghdad in 2003, and the 2006 Department of Justice investigation into Lewis's campaign funding. Researchers may be particularly interested in the subject files, which contain articles singled out by Lewis's staff as being especially important during his career, as well as Lewis's own weekly and bimonthly column.
    Organization and Arrangement
    This subseries is organized in two parts: the first includes the majority of the files and is arranged chronologically; the second is arranged by subject.
    - Press Clippings, 1969 June-1976 May (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 3), 1979 February-May (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 3), 1979 February-May (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings (3 of 3), 1979 February-May (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 3), 1979 June-September (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 3), 1979 June-September (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings (3 of 3), 1979 June-September (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 2), 1979 October-December (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 2), 1979 October-December (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 3), 1980 January-March (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 3), 1980 January-March (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings (3 of 3), 1980 January-March (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 2), 1980 April-June (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 2), 1980 April-June (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 2), 1980 July-September (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 2), 1980 July-September (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 3), 1980 October-1981 August (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 3), 1980 October-1981 August (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings (3 of 3), 1980 October-1981 August (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, 1981 April-1985 December (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 3), 1981 November-1982 April (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 3), 1981 November-1982 April (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings (3 of 3), 1981 November-1982 April (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 3), 1982 February-October (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 3), 1982 February-October (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings (3 of 3), 1982 February-October (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 2), 1982 May-1987 February (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 2), 1982 May-1987 February (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 3), 1982 November-1983 March (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 3), 1982 November-1983 March (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings (3 of 3), 1982 November-1983 March (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 3), 1983 April-September (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 3), 1983 April-September (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings (3 of 3), 1983 April-September (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 3), 1983 October-1984 September (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 3), 1983 October-1984 September (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings (3 of 3), 1983 October-1984 September (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Press Clippings, 1984 October (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Press Clippings, 1984 November (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Press Clippings, 1984 December (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 January (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 February (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 March (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 April (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 May (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 June (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 July (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 August (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 September (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 October (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 November (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings, 1985 December (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 January (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 February (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 March (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 April (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 May (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 June (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 July (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 August (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 September (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 October (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 November (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Press Clippings, 1986 December (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 January (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 February (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 March (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 May (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 June (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 August (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 September (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 October (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 November (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Press Clippings, 1987 December (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 January (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 February (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 March (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 April (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 May (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 June (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 July (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 August (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 September (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 October (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 November (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, 1988 December (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 January (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 February (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 March (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 April (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 May (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 June (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 July (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 August (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 September (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 October (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 November (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings, 1989 December (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings, 1991 June (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings, 1991 September (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 1991 October (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Press Clippings, 1991 November (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Press Clippings, 1991 December (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Local Coverage of Community Forums, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 2), 1994 January-June (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 2), 1994 January-June (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Press Clippings, 1994 June-November (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Press Clippings, 1994 November (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Press Clippings, 1994 December (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 January (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Press Clippings: Inland Empire Elections 2012, Other, 1995-2012 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 February (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 March (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 April (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 May (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 June (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 July (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 August (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 September (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 October (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 November (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 1995 December (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 January (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 February (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 March (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 April (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 May (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 June (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 July (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 August (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 September (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 October (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 November (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Press Clippings, 1996 December (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 January (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 February (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 March (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 April (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 May (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 June (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 July (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 August (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 September (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 October (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 November (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 1997 December (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 1998 January (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 1998 February (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 1998 March (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, 1998 April (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings, 1998 May (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 2), 1998 June (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 2), 1998 June (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings, 1998 July (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings, 1998 August (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings, 1998 September (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings, 1998 October (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings, 1998 November (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 1998 December (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Lewis on F-22 Raptor, 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 January (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 February (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 March (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 April (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 May (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 June (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 July (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 August (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 September (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 October (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 November (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings, 1999 December (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Local Stories on Jerry Lewis, 2000-2003 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 January (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 February (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 March (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 April (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 May (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 June (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 July (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 August (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 September (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 October (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 November (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings, 2000 December (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 January (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 February (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 March (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 April (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 May (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 June (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 July (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 August (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 September (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 October (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 November (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Press Clippings, 2001 December (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 January (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 February (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 March (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 April (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 May (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 June (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 July (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 August (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 September (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 October (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 November (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, 2002 December (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 January (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 February (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 March (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 April (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 May (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 June (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 July (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 August (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 September (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 October (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 November (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Press Clippings, 2003 December (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Lewis As Appropriations Chair, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 January (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 February (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 March (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 April (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 May (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 June (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 July (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 August (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 September (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 October (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 November (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Press Clippings, 2004 December (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Press Clippings, 2005 January (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 2), 2005 February (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 2), 2005 February (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Press Clippings, 2005 March (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Press Clippings, 2005 April (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Press Clippings, 2005 May (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Press Clippings, 2005 June (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Press Clippings, 2005 July (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Press Clippings, 2005 August (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Press Clippings, 2005 September (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Press Clippings, 2005 October (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Press Clippings, 2005 November (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Press Clippings (1 of 2), 2005 December (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Press Clippings (2 of 2), 2005 December (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Press Clippings, 2006 January (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Press Clippings, 2006 February (Box 9, Folder 26)